imenupro.com 2015-03-18

# iMenuPro · Privacy Policy

## SoftCafe iMenuPro

### Privacy Policy

We are committed to protecting your personal information.

Your privacy is extremely important to us, and to better protect you, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices. This notice is available from every page of this website.

#### Personal Information We Collect

This notice applies to personal information collected or submitted when you sign up for the iMenuPro service. If you do not sign up, we do not collect personal information.

  * First/Last name
  * Email address
  * Account password 
  * Credit/Debit card information for billing
  * Billing postal code for verification

#### Credit Card Information

No one at SoftCafe can see your credit card information. We use the secure Stripe payment service. Stripe encrypts your credit card information in their database and is PCI compliant, so you can feel good about how they secure your information. Stripe provides to us the last 4 digits of your credit card only so you can later identify which credit card you are using within our service.

#### How We Use Your Personal Information

We use the information you provide about yourself during sign up and log in to verify your eligibility for the iMenuPro service, to provide customer service during the term of your service, for billing and payment for the service, and to advise you of changes to our service, or new services that we may implement from time to time.

#### Will you ever share my email address?

We will never sell or rent your any of your personal information. Email addresses will only be shared with a third party if required by law or covered in this disclosure. We may occasionally contact you via email with product updates that we feel will improve your experience with the iMenuPro service. These emails will always include a prominent, and effective, unsubscribe link.

#### Information Collected Automatically

We may also receive or collect certain technical and analytic information when you use our website, such as the internet protocol (“IP”) address of your computer, the IP address of your internet service provider, mobile device ID, the date and time you access our website or service, the IP address or URL of the website from which you linked directly to our website, the operating system you are using, the Internet browser you are using, the sections of the website you visit, the website pages read, images viewed, or other content that you may access from the iMenuPro service. This information will not be shared with anyone outside of SoftCafe unless required by law.

#### Securing Your Information

SoftCafe endeavors to safeguard personal information to ensure that such information is kept private. However, unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, the inherent insecurity of the Internet and other factors, may compromise the security of your personal information at any time. Therefore we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information.

#### International Users

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the iMenuPro Service is hosted in the United States. Therefore, your information may be processed and stored in the United States. As a result, United States federal and state governments, courts, or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your information through laws applicable in the United States. Your use of this service or your submission of any personal information to us will constitute your consent to the transfer of your personal information outside of your home country, including the United States, which may provide for different data protection rules than in your country.

#### Children and Minors

The iMenuPro service is not intended for use by minors under the age of 13. We do not knowingly solicit any information from such minors. If you are a parent or legal guardian who discovers that your child has provided us with information without your consent, you may contact us at support@imenupro.com. We will delete such information from our system.

#### Questions?

Please don't hesitate to contact us at support@imenupro.com if you have questions or concerns.
